Morris, James O., Office Files /4073
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- AFL- EC Minutes May 9-15, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- 1924 Campaign Expenses Labor (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Finances (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Howell-Barkley Expenses Feb.-June 1924 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- AFC 1920's Railway Labor Act (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Howell- Barkley: Two Finances (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Material not used in 1st Draft of HB: Two (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Small Railroads Opposition (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Revisions of Command (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Why Carriers Cooperated (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Leftover from "Command" (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Revisions of Victory at Last (Box 29, Folder 38)
- 1926 Act (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Victory at Last (8) (Box 29, Folder 40)
- Victory at Last (10) (Box 29, Folder 41)
- "Victory at Last" Leftovers (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Leftovers from "Victory" (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Atterbury- Bio (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Labor Leaders Assessed by Hooper (Box 30, Folder 2)
- W.S. Carter (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Esch (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Cummins (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Hooper (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Huddleston (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Garretson (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Howell (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Jewell (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Lee (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Keating (Box 30, Folder 12)
- McAdoo (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Warren Stone- Bio (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Plumb (Box 30, Folder 15)
- DB Robertson (Box 30, Folder 16)
- James M. Mead (Box 30, Folder 17)
- John Nolan (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Walber (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Warfield (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Willard (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Wheeler (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Woodrow Wilson: Background (Box 30, Folder 24)
- W. Wilson (Personality) (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Railroad Labor Docs. 1922 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Railroad Labor Docs. 1922 (5) (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Railroad Labor Docs. 1922 (6) (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Railroad Labor Docs. (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Misc. Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 30)
- CPPA (Box 30, Folder 31)
- 1922 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Founding of CPPA (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Labor and Politics 1922 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Labor and Politics 1922 Hoover (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Socialist Party and CPPA- Books (Box 30, Folder 36)
- 4/15/23 Keating- Hillquit Debate on Labor Party, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- Founding CPPA (Box 30, Folder 38)
- AFL 1922 (1) (Box 30, Folder 39)
- AFL 1922 (2) (Box 30, Folder 40)
- CPPA Minutes New York 1923-1924 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Warfield Proposal 1922 (Box 30, Folder 42)
- Notes on Amending "Chiefs Part in Thumb" (Box 30, Folder 43)
- Chiefs (Box 30, Folder 44)
- Conclusion (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Amfed (Jan-Dec. 1923) (Box 30, Folder 46)
- Journal BLF+E Jan-July 1923 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- BLF+E Journal July-Dec. 1923 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- Journal Conductor 1923 (Box 30, Folder 49)
- BLE Journal 1923 (Box 30, Folder 50)
- RLB in Operation 1923 (Box 30, Folder 51)
- AFC 1920's Coal (Box 30, Folder 52)
- Charges of RR Bankrupter (Box 30, Folder 53)
- Plumb or EC (Box 30, Folder 54)
- Plumb or EC (Box 30, Folder 55)
- Plumb Plan or EC (Box 30, Folder 56)
- Plumb or EC (Box 30, Folder 57)
- Plumb or EC Events in Dec. and Jan. 1920 (Box 30, Folder 58)
- House Hearings July 15- Oct. 4 (Box 30, Folder 59)
- Names and Parties (Box 30, Folder 60)
- House Hearings July 15- Oct. 4 (Box 30, Folder 61)
- Opponents of PP (Box 30, Folder 62)
- Senate Hearings 9/19 (Box 30, Folder 63)
- The Nov. and Dec. Conferences (Box 30, Folder 64)
- House Report Nov. 10, 1919 (Box 30, Folder 65)
- House Debate Nov. 11- Nov. 17 (Box 30, Folder 66)
- Chiefs put in Thumb (Box 30, Folder 67)
- Labor in Other Plans (Box 30, Folder 68)
- Chiefs Put in Thumb (1) (Box 30, Folder 69)
- Chiefs Put in Thumb (2) (Box 30, Folder 70)
- Chiefs Put in Thumb (3) (Box 30, Folder 71)
- Chiefs Put in Thumb (5) (Box 30, Folder 72)
- Chiefs Put in Thumb (6) (Box 30, Folder 73)
- Howell- Barkley I (2) (Box 30, Folder 74)
- Howell- Barkley Act I (3) (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Howell- Barkley Act I (4) (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Howell- Barkley Act I (6) (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Howell- Barkley Act I (6) (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Arguments for and vs. Howell- Barkley (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Howell- Barkley: Two (1) (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Howell- Barkley I (1) (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Howell- Barkley: Two (2) (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Command (1) (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Command (2) (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Command (3) (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Command (4) (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Command (5) (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Command (6) (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Victory at Last (1) (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Victory at Last (2) (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Victory at Last (3) (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Victory at Last (4) (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Victory at Last (5) (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Victory at Last (), 1926 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Norris and La Follette 1924 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- La Follette 1924 (2) (Box 31, Folder 22)
- La Follette 1924 (3) (Box 31, Folder 23)
- La Follette 1924 (4) (Box 31, Folder 24)
- La Follette 1924 (5) (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Nye Papers (1923-1924) (Box 31, Folder 26)
- AFL Workmen's Compensation 1924 (Box 31, Folder 27)
- AFL- 1924 ( Feb. 29- May 6) (Box 31, Folder 28)
- AFL- 1924 (July 4- Nov. 26) (Box 31, Folder 29)
- AFL- EC 1924 (Box 31, Folder 30)
- Pres. And V-P Acceptance Speeches 1924 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- R Party Platform 1924 (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Campaign Docs. 1924 (Box 31, Folder 33)
- Hoover Papers 1923 (Box 31, Folder 34)
- Hoover Radio Addresses 9/29, 10/29, 10/31 1924 (Box 31, Folder 35)
- Coolidge Papers (?) from Levner's Term Paper (Box 31, Folder 36)
- W.B. Wilson Papers 1923 (Box 31, Folder 37)
- W.B. Wilson Papers 1924 (Box 31, Folder 38)
- W.B. Wilson Papers 1924 but month and/or day missing (Box 31, Folder 39)
- MacNider Papers 1924 (but mo. and day missing) (Box 31, Folder 40)
- MacNider Papers 1924 (Box 31, Folder 41)
- 1924 Victor Murdock (Box 31, Folder 42)
- Philip Fox La Follette, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 43)
- Nelson, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 44)
- Mahoney, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 45)
- John L. Lewis, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 46)
- Illinois, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 47)
- Wefald, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 48)
- Illinois, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 49)
- 1928 Mack Papers (Box 31, Folder 50)
- Supreme Court Cases (Box 31, Folder 51)
- Empey, 1925-1929 (Box 31, Folder 52)
- NAM 1924 (Box 31, Folder 53)
- 1928 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Nam- Weber (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Introduction- Syrett Term Papers (Box 32, Folder 3)
- La Follette- Wheeler from non-labor papers (Box 32, Folder 4)
  term paper
- Coolidge and Labor- Levner (Box 32, Folder 5)
  term papers
- 1924 Vote Analysis- Halfond (Box 32, Folder 6)
  Term paper
- RR Bro's and Politics in 1920's- Young (Box 32, Folder 7)
- BLE- Arnsdorf (Box 32, Folder 8)
- RR Bro's and Politics in 1920's- Young (Box 32, Folder 9)
- 1924 Campaign (Box 32, Folder 10)
- term papers on Amer. Shortline Rd. Assn. (Box 32, Folder 11)
- term paper on Gompers-Wilson correspondence. (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Term Paper on Meyer London and Victor Berger (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Term paper on 1922-1924 Period (Box 32, Folder 14)
- CCPA- Margolin (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Term Paper on SP and CPPA (Box 32, Folder 16)
- NAM- Weber term paper (Box 32, Folder 17)
- 1924 L-W Campaign term paper (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Analysis 1924 Vote term paper (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Term Paper: "The Railway Carriers and the Railway Labor Act" (Box 32, Folder 20)
- "The Making of a Political Machine: The Railroad Unions Enter Politics" 1920's (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Eldersveld Article (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Railroad Wages and LR, 1900-52__Jones, 1900-1952 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- AFL-EC 1921-1923 of no value (Box 32, Folder 24)
- RLB 1923 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- RLB in Operation 1920 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- RLB 1921 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Misc. Loose Notecards (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Labor and Politics: New Deal to Present (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Labor and Politics up to New Deal (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Misc. Loose Notecards (Box 33, Folder 3)
- "A Spark is Struck! Jack Hall and The Ilwu in Hawaii" (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Plumb or EC (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Senate debate Nov. 13- Dec. 19 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Senate Report 304 Nov. 10 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Senate Debate Nov. 13- Dec. 19 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Senate Debate Nov. 13- Dec. 19 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Conference Report 2/18/20 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Debate on Conference Report, House Feb. 21 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Debate on Conference Report- Senate, Feb. 23 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Effort to Veto E-C (Box 34, Folder 9)
- PP after 1919 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- PP after 1919 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- AFL and Plumb Plan (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Affiliation of R.R. Unions (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Unused Politics 1920, mostly AFL (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Presidential Papers (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Harding Papers (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Railroad Papers, LMDC (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Wilson, Woodrow Microfilm (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Coolidge Papers (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Washington Trip 6/82 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Misc. (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Periodicals (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Chiefs- Draw up bill revision (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Official Documents and Testimony of Howell- Berkley 1924 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- West Branch, Iowa Trip (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Periodicals, looked at (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Howell- Berkley: Round Two (Box 35, Folder 1)
- General Atterbury Takes Command (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Victory At Last (Box 35, Folder 3)
- The Plumb Plan Manuscript (1 out of 6) (Box 35, Folder 4)
- The Plumb Plan Manuscript (2 out of 6) (Box 35, Folder 5)
- The Plumb Plan Manuscript (3 out of 6) (Box 35, Folder 6)
- The Plumb Plan Manuscript (4 out of 6) (Box 35, Folder 7)
- The Plumb Plan Manuscript (5 out of 6) (Box 35, Folder 8)
- The Plumb Plan Manuscript (6 out of 6) (Box 35, Folder 9)
- The Plumb Plan Footnotes (Box 35, Folder 10)